Guide to the Office of Public Affiairs, Yale University, Photographs and Supporting Materials Documenting Events and Activities at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of Public Affiairs, Yale University, photographs and supporting materials documenting events and activities at Yale
1970-1991
RU 236
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.5
(4 boxes)
The materials consists of photographs and supporting materials of events and activities at Yale used in Yale publications.
Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-C (YRG 4-C), Records documenting public information functions of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The materials consists of photographs and supporting materials of events and activities at Yale used in Yale publications.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Public relations; Photographs; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Public relations; Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
- Photographs and supporting materials of commencements, faculty, buildings and grounds, presidents, Freshmen, award receipients, visitors, library collections, students, Accession 1995-A-033 (Box 1–2)
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Photographs taken for use in "WorkWords" and "Professionally Speaking, 1990-1991; Accession 1996-A-034
  - Photographs taken for use in "WorkWords" and "Professionally Speaking, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
- Class Day speech scripts, 1989-1997; Accession 2009-A-074
  - Tom Wolfe, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marian Wright Edelman, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gary Trudeau, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Calvin Trillin, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Jodie Foster, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sargent Shriver, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kurt Schmoke, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Henry Winkler, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - David McCullough, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)